<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Bots Rising</title>
  <subtitle></subtitle>
  <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net</id>
  <link href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net"/>
  <link href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2017-07-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name></name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title/>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/07/26/building-m-uber-engineering-a-high-performance-web-app-for-the-global-market-by-.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/07/26/building-m-uber-engineering-a-high-performance-web-app-for-the-global-market-by-.html</id>
    <published>2017-07-26T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T23:14:42+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html"></content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Expressive launches emotionally responsive avatars (by Khari Johnson)</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/07/12/expressive-launches-emotionally-responsive-avatars-by-khari-johnson.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/07/12/expressive-launches-emotionally-responsive-avatars-by-khari-johnson.html</id>
    <published>2017-07-12T05:28:26Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T23:14:41+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      The vast majority of language exchanged between people isn’t with words — it’s nonverbal&lt;br/&gt;
    That’s why the newly formed startup Expressive is making stylized avatars that mimic body language and human emotion. The avatars detect human emotion through the use of sentiment analysis, or understanding the tone in words used by a human. The avatars then respond with emotional reactions like happiness, sadness, shock, disgust, and anger.&lt;br/&gt;
    Created by Pandorabots, the conversational bot is more than a decade old and on multiple occasions has won the Loebner Prize, an annual international competition for convincing humans they are speaking to a human instead of a bot.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://venturebeat.com/2017/07/11/expressive-ai-launches-emotionally-responsive-avatars/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A Quick Guide to Identify Twitter Bots Using Machine Learning</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/05/27/a-quick-guide-to-identify-twitter-bots-using-machine-learning.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/05/27/a-quick-guide-to-identify-twitter-bots-using-machine-learning.html</id>
    <published>2017-05-27T21:57:00Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T23:14:39+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      Role of Twitter Bots in US Presidential Election&lt;br/&gt;
    Barack Obama’s 29.9% followers might be bots/fake and this number for Mitt Romney was around 21.9%.&lt;br/&gt;
    pro-Trump bots generated four tweets for every pro-Clinton automated account and out-tweeted pro-Clinton bots 7:1 on relevant hashtags during the final debate.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://blog.karna.ai/a-quick-guide-to-identify-twitterbots-using-ai-44ca424cafc?utm_source=forum&amp;amp;utm_medium=group_post&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Data%20Tau%20"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>5 lessons learned from making a banking chatbot (by Sidharth Garg)</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/03/01/5-lessons-learned-from-making-a-banking-chatbot-by-sidharth-garg.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/03/01/5-lessons-learned-from-making-a-banking-chatbot-by-sidharth-garg.html</id>
    <published>2017-03-01T20:59:04Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      Sidarth Garg shares his general learnings from making a banking chatbot.&lt;br/&gt;
    One distinguishing feature of his pilot was the target market: an economically and culturally diverse set of credit union members in Brooklyn. This group of users is probably very different from the tech-savvy users of most other chatbots.&lt;br/&gt;
    Here are his takeaways:&lt;br/&gt;
    1. There is a lot of curiosity&lt;br/&gt;
    Despite probably not knowing too much about chatbots beforehand, people were genuinely interested in learning more about a new “virtual banking assistant”&lt;br/&gt;
    2. Limited exploration&lt;br/&gt;
    Although many people understood the concept of a “banking assistant,” almost no one tried commands that weren’t suggested. Only a handful of people tried asking personal, open-ended questions.&lt;br/&gt;
    3. Chatbots still need a human backup&lt;br/&gt;
    He really believes that having empathy for users is crucial. That means routing the chat to a human when the conversation feels stuck.&lt;br/&gt;
    4. Proactive reengagement&lt;br/&gt;
    The biggest insight to come from his pilot was the need for reminders and reengagement. As with most product launches, the real challenge is user retention and growing periodic usage. This “launch curve” also applied to his pilot: Initial reception was strong but then slowly decreased. This is where smarter technology and marketing can help reverse the course.&lt;br/&gt;
    5. Expect some strange responses&lt;br/&gt;
    As he states:&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
     &amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;
    On the silly side, I got a few expected messages from people asking: “Are you human?” On the more nefarious side, I received a handful of vulgar, emoji-laden messages (some I didn’t even know existed, but I had to applaud their creativity). Perhaps I should add emoji-translation to the next version of Teller.&amp;ldquo;&lt;br/&gt;
    You can read the full article here:&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://venturebeat.com/2017/02/21/5-lessons-learned-from-making-a-banking-chatbot/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Conversational Slack Bots 101 made with Api.ai</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/15/conversational-slack-bots-101-made-with-api-ai.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/15/conversational-slack-bots-101-made-with-api-ai.html</id>
    <published>2017-02-15T14:09:19Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        Api.ai is a so called conversational user platform for building up your own bot solution which connects end user devices and your application with a conversational interface. 
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
        The following article will guide you through the necessary steps in order to get a Slack bot up and running.
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
        In a nutshell
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;D&lt;span style=""&gt;esign conversations&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;span style=""&gt;Start with creating an agent at Api.ai. The agent will be the conversational part of your bot’s brain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Connect to a web service:  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;After your bot learns how to understand people, it needs to start responding. You can connect your bot to a web service via a webhook.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Test: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;In the Api.ai developer account, you can find the test console, where you can try how well your agent understands you already. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Train: it more right away by adding more examples in existing scenarios or create new ones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Create a Slack bot by turning on the Slack Integration and choose message type interaction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;span style=""&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Test in Slack.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
       &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
       &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Publish it&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
        Quite straightforward, you can read the full article here.
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://api.ai/blog/2016/03/17/Slack-Bots-101/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Are chatbots an evolution or a revolution?</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/13/are-chatbots-an-evolution-or-a-revolution.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/13/are-chatbots-an-evolution-or-a-revolution.html</id>
    <published>2017-02-13T11:46:18Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;div&gt;
        The article exploits the hype around chatbots and will outline why there aren’t really evidences that it is a revolution but rather an evolution.
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
        First the article will describe the lessons learnt from China and India. 
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;&amp;ldquo;To predict how chatbots will evolve, we can look to Asia, a region that has led the West in this space. We’ll use WeChat in China and SMS-based messaging in India as examples …&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;… WeChat’s success, though I would argue most of it is not relevant. For example, much of its functionality is through a browser interface rather than a chat interface — hardly a model for the promise of automated chatbots  …&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;… Monetization is focused on payments rather than advertising. Messaging apps occupy a highly personal space, and advertising is ill-suited in this space without risking user backlash. Integrated payments, however, are an important additive part of the user workflow …&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;… Application-to-person (A2P) SMS messaging in India may be a more relevant precedent for today’s chatbots. In India, A2P messages are a ubiquitous aspect of daily life … &lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;i&gt;… This market has evolved in recent years from notification-oriented messages (‘you completed an ATM withdrawal’), to marketing-oriented messages (SMS, not email, is the dominant digital channel), to customer service-oriented messages (‘your order will be delivered today’), and now interaction-oriented messaging (‘tell me my last 3 transactions’).”&lt;/i&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
        As the writer points out the most successful use cases were lightweight — useful information with little cognitive load given the 160-character limit for SMS.
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
        He goes on by reflecting on these experiences, there are a few takeaways that argue for a more evolutionary approach for chatbots in the West:
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Early use cases are likely to be quite simple.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Rich interaction experiences (e.g., buttons, menus) are required to drive complex use cases.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Cross-platform support is critical for widespread adoption, and there are already more than a dozen relevant platforms, including Messenger, WhatsApp, Alexa, iMessage, Skype, Slack, SMS, and email.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Platforms must tread carefully on user acquisition, ensuring it is not too onerous as to hamper growth while ensuring users are not inundated with undesired messages.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Platforms must self-regulate to resist the pull to make chatbots another marketing channel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Payment integration will be a key enabler for consumer monetization.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
       &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
        Read the full article including the Opportunities section here.
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;div&gt;
       &lt;br&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://venturebeat.com/2016/09/01/are-chatbots-an-evolution-or-a-revolution/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>How Can Chatbots Be the Future If They Are Stuck in the 1960s?</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/09/how-can-chatbots-be-the-future-if-they-are-stuck-in-the-1960s.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/09/how-can-chatbots-be-the-future-if-they-are-stuck-in-the-1960s.html</id>
    <published>2017-02-09T06:17:29Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      A reflection of naming bots in the financial industry.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &amp;ldquo;Voices, names, accents — they all influence who we listen to and who we ignore.&lt;br/&gt;
    Banking has always been a male-dominated industry where men&amp;rsquo;s voices are heard the most. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t been uncommon for someone to assume a woman is in an assistant role when, in fact, she is the expert in the room. And now the sexism of yesteryears is bleeding into the frontier of bank innovation: artificial intelligence, or AI.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Read the full article here&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.americanbanker.com/opinion/how-can-chatbots-be-the-future-if-they-are-stuck-in-the-1960s"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What we learned from bots, before they were cool</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/07/what-we-learned-from-bots-before-they-were-cool.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/02/07/what-we-learned-from-bots-before-they-were-cool.html</id>
    <published>2017-02-07T06:05:39Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      An overview of important bot concepts out of the early days of SMS interactions.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &amp;ldquo;Long before Messenger, Whatsapp and Telegram came on the scene, SMS was the most intimate way for a brand to reach a customer. And we must give credit to the brands that had the foresight to experiment with a new technology across this personal communication channel.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br/&gt;
    Some key insights developers learned from those early days building bots.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    1. Scope and expectations&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    It is essential to clearly outline the scope of what the chatbot does, before the user engages with it for the first time. This establishes an appropriate level of expectation ahead of time, and puts the user in a desired frame of mind when communicating with the bot.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    2. Reactive vs Proactive&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    How a user engages with a bot for the first time will determine the bot’s virality and ultimate adoption. There are three basic approaches.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Reactive bots: the customer will see an ad and a method to communicate (SMS shortcode, QR scan, etc), giving them the initiative to reach out. This provides a high level of integrity and respect in your brand communication.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Proactive bots: these message the customer first. They are cool because they are unexpected and can drive a much higher initial engagement rate than reactive bots.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Mixed engagement bots: these combine both approaches. The user will send the initial message, showing their interest to engage. The bot will then take them through a conversational experience to learn more about the user, and eventually serve proactive messages as needed.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    3. Channel&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    As a consumer brand wanting to play the bot game, it makes sense to be where your users are. Probably living inside Messenger, Whatsapp and Snapchat.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    4. Evaluation and metrics&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    As with most emerging technologies, there is a period of time with lots of action but not enough palpable insights on what’s actually working. This is why it’s extremely important to establish a way to evaluate and measure the chatbot experience for brands.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    You can read the full article here&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://venturebeat.com/2016/06/25/what-we-learned-from-bots-before-they-were-cool/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Understanding bots through 4 interface categories</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/28/understanding-bots-through-4-interface-categories.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/28/understanding-bots-through-4-interface-categories.html</id>
    <published>2017-01-28T07:00:41Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      This article introduces four categories for bots in the area of message-based applications. As the author states&lt;br/&gt;
    &amp;ldquo;To promote clarity, journalists, technologists, marketers, and business leaders need to choose their words more carefully in the ongoing conversation on chatbots, messenger bots, virtual assistants, conversational UI, and natural language interfaces (just a small sampling of the various labels these phenomena get slapped with).&amp;rdquo;&lt;br/&gt;
    He is doing that by 4 categories &lt;br/&gt;
    Click navigation: This is the simplest form of messaging bot. Dispensing altogether with custom text-field and voice input, these bots use images, radio buttons, and scripted text to traverse a logical and preset navigation flow.&lt;br/&gt;
    Keyword search: These are slightly more advanced bots that can search for keywords found within text fields or voice search input. Since natural language is not supported, these bots work well for small data sets with a limited number of potential search queries. &lt;br/&gt;
    Keyword search: These are slightly more advanced bots that can search for keywords found within text fields or voice search input. Since natural language is not supported, these bots work well for small data sets with a limited number of potential search queries. &lt;br/&gt;
    Structured phrase matching: Structured phrase matching introduces the notion of natural language understanding (NLU) for short phrases with predictable keyword categories. &lt;br/&gt;
    Unrestricted natural language: This category presents an experience that is much more akin to a human conversation. Unrestricted natural language interfaces understand natural sentences of any structure, whether spoken or typed, and can engage in multipart, dynamically generated dialogue to disambiguate, complete, and resolve queries.&lt;br/&gt;
    You can find the full article (which is accompanied by a helpful infographic) by clicking on the link at the end of this article.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://venturebeat.com/2016/09/28/understanding-bots-through-4-interface-categories/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>On bots, language and making technology disappear</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/27/on-bots-language-and-making-technologydisappear.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/27/on-bots-language-and-making-technologydisappear.html</id>
    <published>2017-01-27T06:47:23Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      This is a very interesting article which is exploiting the impact of naming a bot from a psychological interaction point of view.&lt;br/&gt;
    &amp;ldquo;A name can be a way of expressing trust in an object — or expressing control over it. In design terms, a name is a kind of affordance — a handle we can hold onto.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    When we name the tools we use, we assert control over them; we do that because we want to be the ones having the interaction, doing the job.&lt;br/&gt;
    The digital tools we make live in a completely different psychological landscape to the real world. We can’t get a handle on them, literally. There is no straight line from a tradesman’s hammer he can repair himself to a chatbot designed and built by a design team somewhere in California.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    Names and identity lift the tools on the screen to a level above intuition. They make us see the tool in all its virtual glory, and place it in an entirely different context to the person using it — and not always a relationship that person asks for or appreciates&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    As he states, introducing personality into technology might not be the way we become more comfortable.&lt;br/&gt;
    &amp;quot;There’s another school of thought in design, one that describes it as almost invisible. Siri and Alexa might have been thought of as examples of this type: you can’t really see them, and so they disappear into the background.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    You can find the full article here.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://social.techcrunch.com/2017/01/07/on-bots-language-and-making-technology-disappear/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>wit.ai Bot Engine Key Concepts</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/26/wit-ai-bot-engine-key-concepts.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/26/wit-ai-bot-engine-key-concepts.html</id>
    <published>2017-01-26T21:38:08Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      wit.ai released in this article in April 2016, their vision for conversational bots: an early beta of Bot Engine. Since they joined Facebook in 2014 months ago, the Wit community grew from 6,000 to 21,500 developers. &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    They shared their key concept around building a bot engine, grouped around the following questions&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    - What is the user’s intent?&lt;br/&gt;
    - How should the bot respond?&lt;br/&gt;
    - What actions should it perform?&lt;br/&gt;
    - What question should it ask? &lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    You can find the full article here:&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://wit.ai/blog/2016/04/12/bot-engine"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Bots Landscape evolves</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/26/the-bots-landscape-evolves.html"/>
    <id>https://botsnews.cloudburo.net/2017/01/26/the-bots-landscape-evolves.html</id>
    <published>2017-01-26T07:07:37Z</published>
    <updated>2017-07-26T20:29:35+00:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="row"&gt;
  &lt;div class="article"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;span/&gt;      Amir Shevat from Slack provides an excellent overview how the bot landscape evolved in the recent year.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    The article is accompanied by a bot landscape infographic which provides a good and structured overviw of the market.&lt;br/&gt;
    His take is that we are still very early in this game, and there are still major hurdles to overcome. We are still exploring the best use cases (and business cases) for bots&lt;br/&gt;
    The opportunity for the next year of the bot ecosystem is pretty big, and we might start to see winners in a few segments.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    When it comes to bots for work, there are a lot of opportunities to create the next big thing with bots that assist us in all aspects of work: HR, productivity, finance, sales, support, legal, IT, corporate travel, security, and more.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;br/&gt;
    You can find the article here.&lt;br/&gt;
    &lt;a href="http://venturebeat.com/2016/11/30/the-bots-landscape-evolves-adds-heavyweights-like-google-assistant-funds-14-more-slack-bots/"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
